<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-03-10T01:01:20-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Torrid Games</title><subtitle>&lt;desc&gt;</subtitle><author><name>&lt;author&gt;</name></author><entry><title type="html">About</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/TG" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About" /><published>2024-01-02T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/TG</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/TG"><![CDATA[<p>Torrid Games launched with the iOS game title SurfGod. This game gained attention for its innovative approach, offering a meditative surfing experience aimed at both surfers and non-surfers. In collaboration with oceanic pollution cleanup organizations like Heal the Bay, Torrid Games developed a free version of SurfGod, achieving 20,000 downloads, reflecting the game’s impact and the company’s commitment to raising awareness about oceanic pollution.  Torrid Games is in the process of raising capital to continue this trend at a deeper and broader level.</p>]]></content><author><name>Torrid Games</name></author><category term="facts" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Torrid Games launched with the iOS game title SurfGod. This game gained attention for its innovative approach, offering a meditative surfing experience aimed at both surfers and non-surfers. In collaboration with oceanic pollution cleanup organizations like Heal the Bay, Torrid Games developed a free version of SurfGod, achieving 20,000 downloads, reflecting the game’s impact and the company’s commitment to raising awareness about oceanic pollution. Torrid Games is in the process of raising capital to continue this trend at a deeper and broader level.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/TG_Clay.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/TG_Clay.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>